# ANNA JÍLKOVÁ

Energetic and driven graphic designer with three years of experience in the field. I specialize in working with Adobe programs such as Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign, but I love to expand my skills and keep learning in other programs like Figma. My biggest achievement so far is the graphic design of a large exhibition about the Czech writer Milan Kundera at the Czech Centre in Paris.



Email: hi@annajilkova.com Telephone: +420 722 231 248



## Experiences

Sep 2020 - Present

Graphic designer, Moravian Library

Brnc

During my time in the second largest library in the Czech Republic, I had the privilige to shape the face of this institution and make several interesting exhibitions that traveled not only across the country, but also beyond its borders. However, exhibition design was not the only part of my agenda, I also worked on:

- Promotional items of the Moravian Library
- Promotional graphics for cultural events
- Infographic
- Event planning, which included dealing with foreign guests of the institucion

Sep 2016 – Jun 2020

#### School projects

**Jihlava** 

During my studies I had the opportunity to work on several projects for real clients. One of the projects was a new brand design for a private dental clinic. What practical skills did I take away from my studies?

- Working with Adobe Creative Suite
- Brand design, promotional design and more
- Working with traditional graphic materials such as linocut
- Working with traditional art materials

Education

Sep 2020 – Jun 2023

Bachelor's degree in Ethnology, Masaryk University

Brnc

I have always been interested in human culture, history and traditions, so I decided to study ethnology. It helped me with developing more critical thinking and better communication skills.

Sep 2016 – Jun 2020

High School of Graphic Arts, Graphic design

**Jihlava** 

### Volunteering & courses

Oct 2018 – Oct 2022

Volunteer, Ji.hlava International Documentary Film Festival

**Iihlava** 

- Taking care of other volunteers and visitors of the film festival
- Dealing with directors and other filmmakers
- Helping coordinate the debates after projections

Feb 11 - Mar 18,

Search Inside Yourself Programme

Online

Originally developed at Google, Search Inside Yourself teaches practical mindfulness, emotional intelligence and leadership tools to unlock full potential at work and in life.

Skills

Adobe Programmes - Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign

DaVinci Resolve

Office 365 - Word, PowerPoint, Excel

BrightSign Software

Drawing, Digital Drawing

## Hobbies

One of my greatest passions in life is reading. Constantly expanding my horizons is important to me, so I especially like to read books about self-development. As a graphic designer and overall creative thinker, I have to keep an open mind, which I do not only by reading, but also by experiencing new cultures through travelling and following design trends through different mediums.